rewards1.com 2018-05-29

# Rewards1.com - Your premier source for freebies!

  1. ## Introduction

Rewards1 website and service ("Site and Service") values the privacy of your personal information ("Personal Data"). 

This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") governs the Personal Data you submit to us and demonstrates our alignment with global data privacy regulations and industry best practices regarding the collection and usage of Personal Data. 

Our Privacy Policy applies only to the Personal Data you submit to us and does not cover the Personal Data you give to 3rd party market research companies and advertising networks ("Sponsors"). 

  2. ## Personal Data

    1. **Collection and Use**
      1. We collect your email address when you register with our Site and Service. Your email is used for administrative contact including support correspondence, account issues, prize fulfillment, and other essential Site and Service communication. Your email is also used to notify you of promotions, survey opportunities, upcoming events, and other news about products or services. 
      2. We optionally collect your birthdate, gender and country of residence to better match you with surveys most suitable for you.
      3. We optionally collect your name and address for rewards you request which require delivery, including check payouts and prizes which require shipping. 
      4. We optionally collect your PayPal email for PayPal payouts you request from us.
      5. To complete any survey, offer or promotional, Sponsors may collect Personal Data and demographic information including without limitation your name, address, email, gender, phone number, ethnicity, zip code, income and occupation. Consult with each Sponsor's privacy policy to know how they handle your data privacy. 
    2. **Sharing**
      1. We may share your birthdate and/or gender and/or country of residence with Sponsors to identify surveys, offers and promotions for your consideration. 
      2. We may share your Personal Data when required by law.
      3. We may share your Personal Data with relevant authorities if we reasonably believe there is a potential threat to the health and safety of any person.
      4. We may share you Personal Data to protect our property in situations of suspected fraud, illegal activity, or violations of Terms of Service or Privacy Policy.
      5. We may transfer your information, including Personal Data, in the event of a business merger, acquisition, sale, bankruptcy proceedings or other company ownership change.
    3. **Access and Control**
      1. You may at any time view and update your Personal Data under Account > Personal Info, or visit <http://www.rewards1.com/edit-profile.php#edit_profile_personal>.
      2. You may opt out of promotional emails under Account > Privacy, or visit <http://www.rewards1.com/edit-profile.php#edit_profile_privacy>. Members opting out of promotional emails will still receive administrative emails which are required for Site and Service functionality. 
      3. You may contact us regarding your Personal Data to view or make change requests such as update info, suspend processing, or removal of Personal Data.
      4. You may also close your account under Account > Close, or visit <http://www.rewards1.com/edit-profile.php#edit_profile_accclose>, at which point your Personal Data will be deleted within 30 days.
  3. ## User Information

By visiting or using our Site and Service, we may collect non-personally identifiable information including without limitation IP address, browser and OS type and version, referrer data, url's accessed, and time of use through standard web access logs and header information. This information is used to determine trends, evaluate, and otherwise improve the overall quality of our Site and Service. 
  4. ## User Generated Content

Our Site and Service offers you the opportunity to engage with other members through social community features such as public chat, profile messages, testimonial messages/images/videos, marketplace trades and forum posts. Participation is optional and the information you share may be publicly viewable and is not protected by this Privacy Policy. Additionally, you agree that we may use the data you share publicly for marketing and promotional purposes. 
  5. ## Cookies

Browser cookies are small data files created by websites you visit which are stored on your computer by your web browser. We utilize both session and persistent cookies to provide necessary Site and Service functionality and to offer a seamless user experience. Session cookies allow you to remain logged into the Site and Service, and are deleted after you close your web browser. Persistent cookies are used to remember your settings and preferences, and can be removed or disabled by following the help directions for your specific web browser. 
  6. ## Children's Policy

We comply with the US Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA") governing the collection, storage, and use of personal information from children under 13, and do not accept members under 13 years of age. Minors aged 13 to 17 are required to have parental permission to use this Site and Service. 
  7. ## Data Security

We make every reasonable attempt to ensure the safety and integrity of your Personal Data. Technical and organisational measures are implemented to ensure a level of security appropriate for the collection, storage, processing and transfer of Personal Data. This includes protection against unauthorised access, unlawful processing, alteration, accidental loss or deletion. 
  8. ## Location of Processing

The collection, processing, and storage of Personal Data occurs on servers in the United States. If you are not a resident of the United States and submit Personal Data to us, you consent to the transfer, processing, and storage of your Personal Data in the United States as described by this Privacy Policy. 
  9. ## Contact Us

We welcome your comments or questions. Please contact us or visit <http://www.rewards1.com/contact-us.php>. 

This Policy was last updated: May 22, 2018
